cbspressexpress.com 2017-02-10

# CBS Press Express | CBS Privacy Policy

CBS Press Express

Privacy Policy

Effective Date: June 26, 2014

CBS is committed to protecting your privacy. CBS owns, operates, or provides access to the CBS Press Express web site (the “Site”) that is governed by this privacy policy.  This Privacy Policy describes the types of information collected about you when visit the Site; how your information may be used and when it may be disclosed; how you can control the use and disclosure of your information; and how your information is protected. 

This Privacy Policy applies to information, including contact information, collected about you by the Site. This Privacy Policy does not cover any information collected through any other web site. The Site may contain links to non-CBS web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites, and we recommend that you visit the privacy policies of each web site that you visit.

CBS may ask you for some or all of the following types of information when you register for certain services, access various content or features, or directly contact the web site:

  1.  Contact information, such as name, email address, postal address, phone number, facsimile number, employer and mobile number;
    1.  User name, password, and password reminder questions and answers;
    2.  Age and date of birth;
    3.  Other demographic information, such as gender, job information, and zip code;
    4.  Information for a public profile, such as your interests and the address of your web site;
    5.  Communications preferences, such as which newsletters you would like to receive;
    6.  Search queries;
    7.  In limited circumstances, payment and identity verification information, such as credit card number, social security number or comparable national identifiers, and driver's license number where needed for payment or to access a particular service (e.g., contests);
    8.  Contact information about others when you provide information about others or refer a friend to a particular site or service (note: such information is used solely to facilitate the communications requested);
    9.  Information posted in community discussions and other interactive online features;
    10.  Correspondence you send to us; and
    11.  Information collected about you offline (including via facsimile, mail, or in person).

Information we collect automatically may include:

  1.  Your browser type and operating system;
  2.  Your Internet Protocol (IP) address;
  3.  Sites you visited before and after visiting the Site;
  4.  Web pages and advertisements you view and links you click on within the Site;
  5.  Unique identifiers, including mobile device identification numbers that can identify the physical location of such devices in accordance with applicable law;
  6.  Information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies;
  7.  Information about your interactions with video content, such as the type of content viewed, and information about your interactions with email messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or forwarded;
  8.  Upon request, your bandwidth speed and information about the software programs installed on your computer; and
  9.  Standard server log information.

Information we obtain from other sources. 

Where permitted by applicable law, we may collect information about you from other sources, including through interactive applications (such as mobile devices, third-party services, and embedded video players), from co-branded partners and sites (for example, on our pages on Facebook), and from commercially available sources (such as data aggregators and public databases). The following are examples of information we may collect from other sources:

  1.  Name, postal address, and telephone number;
  2.  Demographic data, such as age, gender, and income;
  3.  If you access third-party services through a Site, or if you access the Site via a third-party service, your username and password for those services and other information available about or collected from you on those services, as described in our overview of third-party social networking services;
  4.  Your interests and purchase behavior;
  5.  Publicly-observed data, such as activities on blogs, videos, and other online postings; and
  6.  Other navigation data, such as web sites visited and advertisements viewed or clicked on.

This privacy policy does not cover the practices of third parties, including those that may disclose information to CBS.  All of the information we collect about you may be combined, including to help us tailor our communications to you and to develop rich online content and services across CBS.

We only use payment and identity verification information, such as credit card numbers, driver's license numbers, social security numbers, or comparable national identifiers as necessary for completing a particular transaction or fulfilling a service (e.g., paid subscriptions or awarding prizes to contest winners) or as otherwise required by law.

We generally use other information we collect about you to:

  1.  Fulfill your requests for products, services, and information, including sending you electronic newsletters, authorizing a purchase, and completing a transaction that you have requested;
    1.  Enable you to participate in features such as television programs, surveys, polls, sweepstakes, and message boards;
    2.  Provide you with electronic newsletters, information, special offers and promotional materials on behalf of CBS, companies within our corporate family, and third parties, in accordance with applicable law;
    3.  Analyze the use of the Site and information about visitors to our Site to understand and improve our service offerings and, in accordance with our sharing policies, discussed below, to produce anonymous or aggregated data and statistics that might help third parties develop their own products and service offerings;
    4.  Customize the content you see when you visit the Site;
    5.  Develop and provide advertising tailored to your interests;
    6.  Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and in accordance with the Terms of Use or an applicable release form; and
    7.  For any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent. 

CBS is committed to maintaining your trust and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share information collected about you.

  1.  CBS may share your information with third-party business partners. 
    1.  CBS may share your information with third-party vendors who help us with specialized services, including customer support, email and text message deployment, business analytics, marketing, and data processing. These third parties are allowed to use your information to help us provide our services and not for any other purpose.
    2.  CBS may share your information with Co-Branded Partners.  Co-Branded Partners are third parties with whom CBS may jointly offer a service or feature. You can tell when you are accessing a service offered by a Co-Branded Partner because the Co-Branded Partner's name will be featured prominently. You may be asked to provide information about yourself to register for a service offered by a Co-Branded Partner. In doing so, you may be providing your information to both us and the Co-Branded Partner, or we may share your information with the Co-Branded Partner. Please note that the Co-Branded Partner's privacy policy may apply to its use of your information.
    3.  CBS may share information we collect about you within the family of CBS Corporation, our parent company, and other CBS-affiliated companies, so CBS can provide you with information about products and services that might interest you.
    4.  CBS may share your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of a CBS entity, a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
    5.  CBS may share your information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, and other law enforcement measures, and to comply with other legal obligations, such as FCC requirements.
    6.  CBS may share your information to protect and defend the legal rights, interests, and safety of CBS, its affiliates, and employees, agents, and contractors (including enforcing our agreements); to protect the safety and security of users of the Site and members of the public; and as otherwise disclosed in CBS’s Terms of Use.
    7.  CBS may share your information with advertisers as described in our overview of CBS advertising.
    8.  CBS may share your information in an aggregated or anonymized fashion with any third parties. This sharing of anonymized or aggregated information will not include information that could be used to individually identify you.

You can opt out of receiving commercial email or text messages from CBS by following the instructions contained in any such message. Please note that even if you unsubscribe to commercial messages, we still may need to send you communications relating to your use of the Site, such as service announcements.

If you choose to share contact information with CBS, you may have the opportunity to update that information. You also may update or amend your information by contacting CBS. If you ask CBS to shut down your account or delete your information, CBS will disable your account within a reasonable period of time. Please note that CBS may need to retain some information about you in order to satisfy CBS legal and security obligations. For example, some of your information may remain in back-up storage even if you ask CBS to delete it. In some cases, you may be entitled under local laws to access or object to the processing of information that CBS holds relating to you.

CBS is committed to protecting your information. CBS has adopted commercially reasonable technical, administrative, and physical procedures to help protect your information from loss, misuse, and alteration. Please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We want you to feel confident providing your information but CBS cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit. Please refer to the U.S. Federal Trade Commission's web site for information on how to protect yourself from identity theft.

CBS is headquartered in the United States and has affiliate offices and partners in other countries. Information you provide to CBS or CBS obtains as a result of your use of the Site or participation in CBS programs may be collected in your country and subsequently transferred to the United States or another country in accordance with applicable law. The privacy and data protection laws in another country may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By using the Site or providing CBS with your information, you consent to the collection, international transfer, storage, and processing of your information.

When you select a link to a third party web site from the Site (for example, if you link to Pay Pal in order to pay for a product or service offered on the Site), you will be leaving the Site. Any information that you disclose on the third party site will be governed by that site's privacy policy.

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and service offerings. If we modify our Privacy Policy, we will update the "Effective Date" and such changes will be effective upon posting, applied retroactively.

Some CBS Sites enable users to submit their own content for use in contests, blogs, on-air radio and TV broadcasts, online audio and video streams, videos, message boards, and other functions. Publication of User Generated Content on the CBS Sites is subject to our Terms of Use or the applicable release form. Please remember that any information you disclose becomes public information and exercise caution when deciding to disclose your contact, financial, and other information in a submission. CBS cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Privacy Policy, the law, or your personal privacy and safety. CBS may also engage a third party to provide some of the services associated with the blogs, message boards and similar functions. This third party will collect and host the information that you submit to the CBS Sites but will not use any of this information for purposes other than providing the service.

Residents of the State of California may request a list of all third parties to which a CBS Web Site has disclosed certain information during the preceding year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want such a list, please contact CBS. For all requests, you must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the body of your request and include the name of the CBS Web Site with respect to which you are requesting the information, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please note that CBS will not accept requests via the telephone, mail, or by facsimile, and CBS is not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact your account representative. You may also submit questions or comments using the postal address listed below:

CBS Broadcasting Inc.

51 West 52 Street

New York, NY 10019

Attn: Law Department

Tel: 212-975-4321

E-Mail: [DMDesignatedAgent@cbs.com](mailto:DMDesignatedAgent%40cbs.com) 

* * *
